Rare Pamphlet Collection 6034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 14, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Marx as an economist, 1945; Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Author: Maurice Dobb
- Box: 14, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Trade Union problems, 1941; Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Author: Farrell Dobbs
  - Item 2: Recent trends in the labor movement, 1968; Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Box: 14, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Get wise - organize: What every young steel worker should know, 1937; Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Author: David Doran; William Z. Foster
- Box: 15, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The movement of wages and the future of prices, 1925; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Paul Howard Douglas
  - Item 2: The modern technique of mass production, 1927; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: Address before the Academy of Political Science in the city of New York at its semi-annual meeting on "stabilizing business," April 8, 1927
  - Item 3: The Columbia Conserve Company: a unique experiment in industrial democracy, 1926; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Box: 15, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Civil liberties: "the direct and daring course", 1947; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: William O. Douglas
- Box: 15, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Draft for a program for the Socialist Party of the United State, 1935; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Author: Socialist Party (U.S.). Left Wing Section
    Notes: Formulated by the Left Wing at the Socialist Call Institutes, Bound Brook, N.J., Sept. 7-8, Chicago, Ill., Oct. 19-20.
- Box: 15, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Draft specifications: Library series, GS-14-0, Library Assistant; GS-1410-0, Librarian, 1952; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Author: Special Libraries Association
    Notes: Prepared by the Subcommittee on Revision of the Library Class Specifications, Professional Activities Committee, Washington, D.C., Chapter Special Libraries Association.
- Box: 15, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: ABC of Marxism: outline text for class and self study, 1946; Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Author: Hal Draper
- Box: 15, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The population problem and world depression, 1936; Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Author: Louis I. Dublin
- Box: 15, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Vive l'unite de la classe ouvrie`re de France, 1945; Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Author: Jacques Duclos
- Box: 15, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Life and labor in the Soviet Union, 1937; Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Author: Robert W. Dunn; George Wallace
  - Item 2: What war means to the workers: answering the question, will war bring back prosperity?, 1934; Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Author: Robert W. Dunn
  - Item 3: Spying on workers, 1933; Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Company unions today, 1935; Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: American company unions, 1926; Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Author: Robert W. Dunn; William Z. Foster
- Box: 15, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Religion and American democracy, 1959; Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Author: Roy F. Nichols
- Box: 15, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Gastonia, citadel of the class struggle in the new South, 1929; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Author: William F. Dunne
  - Item 2: The threat to the labor movement: the conspiracy against the trade unions: efficiency unions for the bosses or effective unions for the workers, 1927; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The British strike: its background, its lessons, 1926; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: The Supreme Court's challenge to labor: the N.I.R.A. decision a signal for intensified attacks on the workers, 1935; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: The great San Francisco general strike, 1934; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Worker correspondents: what, when, where, why, how?, 1927; Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Box: 15, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Work for the workers, 1876; Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Author: Charles Meredith Du Puy
- Box: 15, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Marxism after fifty years, 1933; Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Author: R. Palme Dutt
- Box: 15, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Chartist movement, 1944; Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Author: Salme A. Dutt
- Box: 15, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A paradox explained, 1900; Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Author: George A. Eastman
- Box: 15, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A letter to Americans in Europe, 1859; Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Author: Max Eastman
- Box: 15, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Youth and the trade unions, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Author: Fred Eastwood
- Box: 15, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Trades unionism in the United States, 1742-1905: bulwark of capitalism or framework of socialism?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Author: Justus Ebert
- Box: 15, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Should organized labor take sides politically?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Author: Kermit Eby; Maurice R. Franks
- Box: 15, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Economic mobilization, 1941; Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Box: 15, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Women on the job: the communist view, 1973; Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Author: Judy Edelman
  - Item 2: Women on the job: a Marxist-Leninist view, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Box: 15, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: American education and the search for equal opportunity, 1965; Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Author: Educational Policies Commission
- Box: 16, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Notes on Marxism, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: S. M. Ehrenhalt
- Box: 16, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The struggle for revolutionary socialism, 1934; Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Author: Henryk Ehrlich; Haim Kantorovitch; Anna Bercowitz
  - Item 2: The living record of two leaders of labor: an unanswerable refutation of their executioners charges, 1943; Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Author: Erlich-Alter Memorial Conference
    Notes: Henryk Erlich, born 1882; Victor Alter, born 1890, executed-December 1942
- Box: 16, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Our reply to the Royal Commission on Unemployment, 1931; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: S. Elias
- Box: 16, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Marxism's hostile children: Leninism and Socialism, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: George J. Eliasberg
- Box: 16, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A remedy for industrial warfare, 1910; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Charles William Eliot
- Box: 16, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A printer tells the president how to create more jobs than men without cost to government, 1935; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Author: H. Ellenoff
- Box: 16, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Human engineering, 1920; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: Harrington Emerson
    Notes: Address before the Harvard Liberal Club of Boston, May 7, 1920.
  - Item 2: Efficient lives, 1916; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Notes: Address delivered before the Business Men's League of St. Louis, January 5th, 1916
  - Item 3: Modern patriotism, 1914; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Notes: Address delivered before the CivicLeague of Cleveland, February 28th, 1914
- Box: 16, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employment management: its rise and scope, 1920; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Author: Federal Board for Vocational Education
    Notes: The organization of an employment department. January, 1920
- Box: 16, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Enemy at home!, 1943; Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Box: 16, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The British labour movement, 1934; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Author: Friedrich Engels
  - Item 2: The British labour movement, 1940; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Socialism, Utopian and Scientific, 1908; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Author: Friedrich Engels; Edward Aveling
  - Item 4: Ludwig Feuerbach and the outcome of classical German philosophy, 1941; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Box: 16, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Engineering prospects and wages: a memorandum issued by the Communist Party, 1945; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Author: The Communist Party
- Box: 16, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A tale of two workers, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Author: David Engelstein; Carl Hirsch
- Box: 16, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Equality, land and freedom: a program for Negro liberation, 1933; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Author: League of Struggle for Negro Rights
    Notes: Draft submitted by the National Council of the League of Struggle for Negro Rights
- Box: 16, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: William Z. Foster: fool or faker?, 1923; Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Author: Gifford Ernest
- Box: 16, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A draft proposal for an Anarchist Black Cross and manifesto, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Author: Lorenzo Komboa Ervin
- Box: 16, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A lecture on the working men's party, 1830; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Author: Edward Everett
    Notes: First delivered October sixth, before the Charlestown Lyceum, and published at their request.
- Box: 16, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The fair wages clause: an explanatory statement, 1934; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Box: 16, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The relationship of impaired physical condition to accidents, 1915; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: C. G. Farnum
- Box: 16, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Truth and myth about America, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Box: 16, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Capitalism or communism?: which way for us?, 1948; Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Author: Harry Desmond Farren
- Box: 16, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Where do the union men get off?, 1921; Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Author: Charles Norman Fay
- Box: 16, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: How do the Communists work?, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Author: Victor Feather
- Box: 16, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Commission on the church and social service: message for Labor Sunday, 1919, Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Box: 16, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Communism and union labor: where do you stand?, 1937; Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Author: Raymond T. Feely
- Box: 16, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Health care cost: a distorted issue, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Author: Rashi Fein
- Box: 16, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Employers!: FEPC is on your doorstep., 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Box: 16, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Substitutes for the strike; an appraisal, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Author: John Bodley Ferguson
- Box: 17, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: International control of basic industries, 1950; Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Author: Wilfred Fienburgh
- Box: 17, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The New York elections and the fight against Jim Crow, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Author: David Coolidge
- Box: 17, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Youth stands ready!: a symposium of the views of young America, 1941; Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Box: 17, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Consider the laundry workers, 1937; Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Author: Jane Filley; Therese Mitchell
- Box: 17, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The collapse of the Seabury investigation, 1932; Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Author: Nathan Fine; Morris Hillquit
  - Item 2: Trade unionism in theory and practice, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Author: Nathan Fine
- Box: 17, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The dilemma of the Supreme Court: is the N.R.A. constitutional?, 1933; Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Author: Maurice Finkelstein
- Box: 17, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Keeping America strong; a talk., 1949; Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Author: Harvey Samuel Firestone
    Notes: Executives Club of Chicago, Feb. 18, 1949.
- Box: 17, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: First national directory of "rightist" groups, publications and some individuals in the United States (and some foreign countries), 1955; Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Box: 17, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Is this a war for freedom?, 1940; Publication (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Author: Ernst Fischer
- Box: 17, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Stalin and Hitler; the reasons for and the results of the Nazi-Bolshevik Pact, 1940; Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Author: Louis Fischer
- Box: 17, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Chicago: organizing the unemployed, 1964; Publication (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Author: Richard Flacks
- Box: 17, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Report of University of Iowa Conference on Employment Problems of Working Women, 1963; Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Author: John J. Flagler; Mario F. Bognanno; Craig Lloyd
    Notes: Held at Iowa Memorial Union, Iowa City, Iowa, May 10-11, 1963
- Box: 17, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: British trade unionism, 1948; Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Author: Allan D. Flanders
  - Item 2: Wage policy in war-time, 1942; Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: The battle for production, 1941; Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Box: 17, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Security, civil liberties and unions, 1956; Publication (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Author: Harry Fleischman; Joyce Lewis Kornbluh; Benjamin D. Segal; William F. Schnitzler
- Box: 17, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The strike of the textile workers in Lodz, 1933; Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Author: W. Florianski
    Notes: March-April, 1933
- Box: 17, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Daughters of America: Ella Reeve Bloor, Anita Whitney, 1942; Publication (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Author: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn
- Box: 17, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Women in the war, 1942; Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Coal miners and the war, 1942; Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Debs, Haywood, Ruthenberg, 1939; Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Labor's own William Z. Foster; a Communists fifty years of working-class leadership and struggle, 1949; Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Debs and Dennis, fighters for peace, 1950; Publication (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Box: 17, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The final secret of Pearl Harbor, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Author: John T. Flynn
- Box: 17, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Changes and trends in child labor and its control, 1938; Publication (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Author: Homer Folks
- Box: 17, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A plan for coal: being the report to the colliery owners, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Author: Robert Foot
- Box: 17, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Syndicalism, 1913; Publication (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Author: Earl C. Ford; William Z. Foster
- Box: 17, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Has the non-unionist a right to work how, when, and where he pleases?, 1904; Publication (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Author: Frank K. Foster
- Box: 17, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Old King Cole in trouble, 1926; Publication (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Author: William Trufant Foster; Waddill Catchings
  - Item 2: Doctors, dollars and disease, 1938; Publication (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Author: William Trufant Foster
  - Item 3: Progress and plenty, A way out of the dilemma of thrift, 1930; Publication (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Box: 17, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Strike strategy, 1926; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
    Author: William Z. Foster
  - Item 2: The steel workers and the fight for labor's rights, 1952; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: The strike situation and organized labor's wage and job strategy, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: The Watson-Parker law: the latest scheme to hamstring railroad unionism, 1927; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: The meaning of the 9-party Communist conference, 1947; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Trade unionism: the road to freedom, 1921; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: In defense of the Communist Party and the indicted leaders, 1949; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Wrecking the labor banks: the collapse of the labor banks and investment companies of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1927; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: The trade unions and the war, 1940; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Labor and the Marshall plan, 1948; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: N.Y. Herald Tribune's 23 questions about the Communist Party answered by William Z. Foster, 1948; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Steel workers and the war, 1942; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: A manual of industrial unionism, organizational structure and policies, 1937; Publication (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Box: 18, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The crisis in the Socialist party, 1936; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The revolutionary crisis of 1918-1921: in Germany, England, Italy and France, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Questions and answers on the Piatakov-Radek trial, 1937; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Little brothers of the big labor fakers, 1931; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: Report of a speech against the Conference For Progressive Labor Action, made in New Star Casino, New York City, on May 10, 1931
  - Item 5: The railroaders' next step--amalgamation, 1922; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: What means a strike in steel, 1937; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The bankruptcy of the American labor movement, 1922; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Your questions answered on politics, peace, economics anti-semitism, race prejudice, religion, trade unionism, Americanism, democracy, socialism, communism., 1939; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Railroad workers forward!, 1937; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Soviet trade unions and allied labor unity, 1943; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Organizing methods in the steel industry, 1936; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Acceptance speeches: William Z. Foster, candidate for president and Banjamin Gitlow, candidate for vice-president of the Workers (Communist) Party, 1928; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Author: Communist Party of the United States of America.
  - Item 13: The work of the Soviet trade unions in the field of social insurance of the workers, 1945; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Author: A. I. Gorbunov
- Box: 18, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Organizing methods in the steel industry, 1936; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Problems of organized labor today, 1946; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: A letter to Congress: defeat the anti-labor Smith bill!, 1952; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Trade unions in America, 1925; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Author: William Z. Foster; James Patrick Cannon; Earl Browder
  - Item 5: Industrial unionism, 1936; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The war crisis: questions and answers, 1940; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Stop wage-cuts and layoffson the railroads: a reply to President T.C. Cashen of the Switchmens Union of North America, 1946; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Capitalism, Socialism, and the War., 1940; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Roosevelt heads for war, 1940; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Halt the railroad wage cut, 1938; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Box: 18, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A manual of industrial unionism, organizational structure and policies., 1937; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Industrial unionism, 1936; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The strike situation and organized labor's wage and job strategy, 1945; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Problems of organized labor today, 1946; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Wrecking the labor banks: the collapse of the labor banks and investment companies of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1927; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: In defense of the Communist Party and the indicted leaders, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Soviet Union, friend and ally of the American people, 1941; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Organized labor and the Fascist danger, 1947; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: A letter to Congress: defeat the anti-labor Smith bill!, 1952; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Labor and the war, 1942; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Box: 18, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Amalgamation, 1923; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Author: Jay Fox
- Box: 19, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The miner's case, 1935; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Author: Ben Francis
- Box: 19, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Strikes and war! war is hell!: an essay on arbitration of labor troubles, 1900; Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Author: Charles Francis
- Box: 19, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Miners unite!: for one class struggle union, 1934; Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Author: B. Frank
- Box: 19, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: National defense, 1936; Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Author: John Franklin
- Box: 19, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: No friend of labor: the ACTU in the labor unions, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Author: James Morton Freeman
- Box: 19, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor in politics, 1932; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Author: John P. Frey